[{"answer": "Oh, very.", "docId": "120706pmt", "aSentId": 18, "question": "Was it emotional?", "qSentId": 17}, {"answer": "You should -- you're definitely allowed to call me Todd.", "docId": "120706pmt", "aSentId": 61, "question": "Am I allowed to call you Todd?", "qSentId": 60}, {"answer": "Well, you know, my first reaction was -- it was horrifying, you know.", "docId": "120706pmt", "aSentId": 72, "question": "When you heard what has happened, what was your reaction?", "qSentId": 71}, {"answer": "Yes, I knew Whitney.", "docId": "120706pmt", "aSentId": 77, "question": "Did you know Whitney well?", "qSentId": 76}, {"answer": "You know, I -- I was thinking about it and it was the only way that I felt -- I would feel comfortable proceeding with the show and celebrating all of these other musicians, because it was about trying to find that fine balance between celebrating her legacy, giving love to this wonderful, amazing entertainer, and, at the same time, respecting all of these young artists and all of these established artists who were either nominated for Grammys or performing on the show and not putting them in the position where they have to perform at a memorial.", "docId": "120706pmt", "aSentId": 109, "question": "What gave you that idea to do that?", "qSentId": 108}, {"answer": "Of course I do.", "docId": "120706pmt", "aSentId": 170, "question": "Do you understand the particular pressure, as a former -- that led her to enter that spiral of self-abuse towards the end?", "qSentId": 169}, {"answer": "Well -- well, yes, you drift away.", "docId": "120706pmt", "aSentId": 283, "question": "Was music always your first love?", "qSentId": 282}, {"answer": "Whatever goal I'm going -- I want to achieve, achieving it", "docId": "120706pmt", "aSentId": 344, "question": "What is it to you?", "qSentId": 343}, {"answer": "I'm not saying it's going to happen imminently.", "docId": "120706pmt", "aSentId": 352, "question": "Oh, God, I don't even want to think about that, right?", "qSentId": 351}, {"answer": "Well, you're doing a hell of a lot.", "docId": "120706pmt", "aSentId": 377, "question": "But, you know, things -- all being relative and everything being even, it's what you don't do that you'll ultimately regret, you know?", "qSentId": 376}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120706pmt", "aSentId": 379, "question": "My Connect Studio is available now?", "qSentId": 378}, {"answer": "You know what, I'm working on it.", "docId": "120706pmt", "aSentId": 395, "question": "When is the new album out?", "qSentId": 394}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120706pmt", "aSentId": 421, "question": "Is she here?", "qSentId": 420}, {"answer": "Well you said to keep him busy.", "docId": "120706pmt", "aSentId": 427, "question": "Ann Marie, what did you do?", "qSentId": 426}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120706pmt", "aSentId": 434, "question": "Do you get sick of the degrees of separation?", "qSentId": 433}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120706pmt", "aSentId": 450, "question": "Did you know she was the one?", "qSentId": 449}, {"answer": "Oh, yes, absolutely.", "docId": "120706pmt", "aSentId": 471, "question": "Do you remember the first time you met him?", "qSentId": 470}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "120706pmt", "aSentId": 487, "question": "Is it luck and just finding the right person?", "qSentId": 486}, {"answer": "You know, I think we did just get lucky, but I also think that we have the same priorities and I think that helps a lot because we know that our relationship has to be sort of the primary relationship and the primary purpose of our lives in a way, even though we have so many other parts of our lives that are important.", "docId": "120706pmt", "aSentId": 492, "question": "I mean, do you have a certain way that you are with each other that just works?", "qSentId": 491}, {"answer": "It was -- it was scary.", "docId": "120706pmt", "aSentId": 498, "question": "What was it like?", "qSentId": 497}, {"answer": "They are -- my son is about to turn 23 and my daughter is 20.", "docId": "120706pmt", "aSentId": 520, "question": "How old are they now?", "qSentId": 519}, {"answer": "I don't think they know any better.", "docId": "120706pmt", "aSentId": 527, "question": "Do they find it hard being the products of two famous acting stars?", "qSentId": 526}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120706pmt", "aSentId": 536, "question": "It slightly blurs the line, doesn't it?", "qSentId": 535}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120706pmt", "aSentId": 543, "question": "Will you dance with me?", "qSentId": 542}, {"answer": "I drink a lot of water.", "docId": "120706pmt", "aSentId": 551, "question": "How do you stay so ridiculously youthful?", "qSentId": 550}, {"answer": "Not ten hours a day, but I do like to exercise.", "docId": "120706pmt", "aSentId": 556, "question": "How do you get to look like this?", "qSentId": 555}, {"answer": "No, I don't think it is weird.", "docId": "120706pmt", "aSentId": 571, "question": "It is quite weird, actually, isn't it?", "qSentId": 570}, {"answer": "No, I think I could have better bone structure.", "docId": "120706pmt", "aSentId": 578, "question": "Is that the secret?", "qSentId": 577}, {"answer": "Yes, make this quick and brutal.", "docId": "120706pmt", "aSentId": 588, "question": "Is that still a topic of interest?", "qSentId": 587}, {"answer": "So a gun with one bullet, walking down the street, you wouldn't --", "docId": "120706pmt", "aSentId": 596, "question": "Can you say that?", "qSentId": 595}, {"answer": "I love Obama.", "docId": "120706pmt", "aSentId": 620, "question": "Are you an Obama fan generally?", "qSentId": 619}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "120706pmt", "aSentId": 629, "question": "Are you one of these people that I'm going to go and vote?", "qSentId": 628}, {"answer": "Absolutely, 100 percent.", "docId": "120706pmt", "aSentId": 631, "question": "You feel strongly?", "qSentId": 630}, {"answer": "Always.", "docId": "120706pmt", "aSentId": 641, "question": "Are you worried that the Republicans will get in?", "qSentId": 640}, {"answer": "I need to learn more about him, I think.", "docId": "120706pmt", "aSentId": 644, "question": "What do you think of Mitt Romney?", "qSentId": 643}, {"answer": "You know, I will be voting for Obama.", "docId": "120706pmt", "aSentId": 646, "question": "What is your gut feeling?", "qSentId": 645}, {"answer": "I try to be.", "docId": "120706pmt", "aSentId": 648, "question": "You're very diplomatic, aren't you?", "qSentId": 647}, {"answer": "I'm not as good at it -- I'm not as diligent about it as I should be.", "docId": "120706pmt", "aSentId": 654, "question": "Do you like Twitter?", "qSentId": 653}, {"answer": "It is vaguely terrifying, absolutely.", "docId": "120706pmt", "aSentId": 658, "question": "Or is it -- for any artist, is it sort of vaguely terrifying as well?", "qSentId": 657}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120706pmt", "aSentId": 683, "question": "Isn't that amazing?", "qSentId": 682}, {"answer": "Well, it has been the end since December.", "docId": "120706pmt", "aSentId": 687, "question": "How do you feel about this being the end?", "qSentId": 686}, {"answer": "EDGWICK: Oh, very.", "docId": "120706pmt", "aSentId": 707, "question": "Was it emotional?", "qSentId": 706}, {"answer": "Yeah, well, I'm seeing a lot of plays.", "docId": "120706pmt", "aSentId": 721, "question": "What are you doing now with all your free time?", "qSentId": 720}, {"answer": "I think the best -- one of the best moments of my career was working with Paul Newman in \"Mr. and Mrs. Bridge.\"", "docId": "120706pmt", "aSentId": 731, "question": "What has been the best moment of your career, the moment if I could replay it for you right now, you would choose?", "qSentId": 730}, {"answer": "His advice about kids was -- I remember he looked at me -- I had -- Travis was two months old when I did \"Mr. and Mrs. Bridge.\"", "docId": "120706pmt", "aSentId": 746, "question": "What was his advice about kids?", "qSentId": 745}, {"answer": "My big ambition is to work in film with great directors.", "docId": "120706pmt", "aSentId": 758, "question": "Do you have a big ambition, a particular project or something that you would really love to do?", "qSentId": 757}, {"answer": "Alexander Pain.", "docId": "120706pmt", "aSentId": 760, "question": "Who is the number one?", "qSentId": 759}, {"answer": "I think every movie he makes is so other, so brilliant and so spontaneous, and so real and so -- and the characters.", "docId": "120706pmt", "aSentId": 762, "question": "Why him?", "qSentId": 761}, {"answer": "We've -- I've met him several times and auditioned for him several times.", "docId": "120706pmt", "aSentId": 766, "question": "Have you had any conversations?", "qSentId": 765}, {"answer": "Yes, a few times, yes.", "docId": "120706pmt", "aSentId": 768, "question": "He's rejected you?", "qSentId": 767}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "120706pmt", "aSentId": 770, "question": "What was he thinking?", "qSentId": 769}, {"answer": "Kind of.", "docId": "120706pmt", "aSentId": 781, "question": "Is that the dream ticket?", "qSentId": 780}, {"answer": "Yes, that would be amazing.", "docId": "120706pmt", "aSentId": 784, "question": "Can you imagine that?", "qSentId": 783}, {"answer": "I always say to Kev, where is my \"Dead Man Walking.\"", "docId": "120706pmt", "aSentId": 786, "question": "What if you both won Oscars on the same year?", "qSentId": 785}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120706pmt", "aSentId": 824, "question": "Will you please, please marry me?", "qSentId": 823}]